INDHUJA KOTHAPALLY

Hyderbad, India | (+91) 9381583649 Indhuja2420@gmail.com | LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Quality Analyst with overall 2+ years of experience in developing test automation plans, strategies, and scripting
scenarios in Verizon applications. Proficiently used Selenium Web Driver using Java to create effective test scripts,
demonstrating practical experience in the field. Strong knowledge of object-oriented programming and Java skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Programming Languages:** C, C++, Java, Python.
- Tools and frameworks: Selenium using Java, TestNG, Maven, qtest, Tapsium, JIRA, Postman, Appium.
- **IDEs:** Eclipse, VS Code.
- Testing & Debugging: Unit testing, Regression testing, UAT, Sanity testing, Smoke testing, API testing and debugging software interactions.
- Methodologies: SDLC, STLC, Agile Scrum, Requirement Analysis.
- **Database** : MongoDB, SQL.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CONGNIZANT | Hyderabad, IN

Dec 2022-Present

Role: Program Analyst | Project: Verizon

- Developed and executed test scripts based on scenarios and stabilized code for new UI changes in every handoff and Enterprise release using **selenium with java** on different flows in Verizon applications.
- Coordinated regression testing utilizing Selenium (Java), Tapsium, and qTest, managing comprehensive test suites
 containing over 1200 test cases. Created detailed test sets, prioritized tests, and improved script design to ensure
 efficient testing processes.
- Based on test scenarios and pre requirements framed data query using **Robo3T** and implemented in the scripts.
- Executed end to end test scenarios in automation and manual during Enterprise Release and reported bugs if the flow is not working as expected.
- Worked with team to reach client requirements and deliverables in Enterprise release and other releases.
- Used **GITLAB** for seamless integration of code into a specific branch.
- Used Jenkins to automate and integrate testing scripts.

Role: Program Analyst Trainee | Project: Verizon

June 2023 – June 2024

- Used **Selenium Web Driver with Java** to create effective test scripts, demonstrating practical experience in the field.
- Used Robo3T to interact with data.
- Used Postman to automate and integrate testing scripts.

Role: Internship

Dec 2022 - May 2023

- Trained on various courses: C, Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, Functional Testing, Selenium, Basics of Spring Framework, and Page Object Model.
- Automated cognizant web portals using selenium with java.
- Automated various web and mobile applications to test all the functionalities of the website I used data driven framework and testNG.
- Used Appium tool for mobile automation testing.

EDUCATION

- B. Tech computer science and Engineering with a GPA of 7.30 from VBIT (2022), Hyderabad.
- Higher Secondary Education (12th) in science with an aggregate of 93.3% from Sri Chaitanya (2018), Hyderabad.
- Secondary Education (10th) with an aggregate of 95% from St JOSEPH'S High School (2016), Hyderabad.